moviesfanatic.com 2017-06-06

# 

MOVIESFANATIC.COM PRIVACY POLICY

We at moviesfanatic.com take your privacy seriously. This document contains moviesfanatic.com's Privacy Policy ("Policy"). This Policy details how moviesfanatic.com receives, collects and uses information in connection with moviesfanatic.com (the "Site"). 

Collection and Use of Information

moviesfanatic.com does not automatically collect any personally identifiable information, such as names, e-mail addresses, gender, age, address, telephone numbers, login names and passwords or other self-identifying information ("Personal Information"). 

However, if a user wishes to be contacted regarding any offers, updates, newsletters or service related announcements, moviesfanatic.com may request that a the user provide an e-mail address. In this case, by providing their e-mail address to moviesfanatic.com, such user explicitly authorizes moviesfanatic.com to send the user communications. 

moviesfanatic.com may use cookies on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are at moviesfanatic.com's Site. 

Like many Internet sites, moviesfanatic.com uses Cookies to be able to analyze Site usage, improve content, customize the Site's content and layout and for other customer service purposes. moviesfanatic.com's use of cookies is in not linked to any Personal Information. 

moviesfanatic.com may automatically receive and record certain non-personally identifiable information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type and version, internet service provider (ISP), cookie information, and the webpage that a user visits. 

moviesfanatic.com collects non-personally identifiable information for general purposes, including but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user movements, ongoing research, and providing anonymous reporting to internal and external clients. moviesfanatic.com will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with aggregate data of its users. 

Sharing and Disclosure of Information

moviesfanatic.com does not rent, sell, or share any information about you with any third-parties. 

However, moviesfanatic.com may disclose your Personal Information if moviesfanatic.com believes such action is necessary to: 

  * (a) comply with the law or legal process served on moviesfanatic.com;
  * (b) protect and defend the rights or property of moviesfanatic.com (including the enforcement of our agreements); or
  * (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of moviesfanatic.com services or members of the public.

Security and Protection of Personal Information

moviesfanatic.com takes reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. 

Although moviesfanatic.com cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, moviesfanatic.com implements physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the Personal Information. For example, Personal Information is protected by secured computer networks and access to the Personal Information is limited to a few authorized employees and personnel. 

However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. 

Change or Removal of Information

As previously mentioned, Ifa user wishes to be contacted regarding any offers, updates, newsletters or service related announcements, and provides an e-mail address, such user explicitly authorizes moviesfanatic.com to send the user communications. 

If a user's e-mail address changes, a user may correct such information by sending an e-mail to [support@moviesfanatic.com](mailto:support@moviesfanatic.com) with the change request. Alternatively, the user may contact moviesfanatic.com using the contact information listed below. 

If a user no longer wishes to receive e-mail communication from moviesfanatic.com, such as offers, updates and newsletters, a user may opt-out of receiving such communications by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication. 

In addition, a user can remove their e-mail address at any time by sending an e-mail with the subject line of OPT-OUT to [support@moviesfanatic.com](mailto:support@moviesfanatic.com) or contacting us using the contact details listed at the bottom of this Policy. 

Business Transitions

In the event that moviesfanatic.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred in the transaction. 

moviesfanatic.com will post a notice on this website of any such change in ownership or control of the Personal Information moviesfanatic.com may have. This notice will be posted prior to such transfer. 

Updates and Changes to this Privacy Policy

From time to time, moviesfanatic.com may revise this Policy. moviesfanatic.com will post the revised Policy on the Site, so that users can always be aware of what information moviesfanatic.com collects, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed. 

How ToContact Us

moviesfanatic.com is owned and operated by Aztec Media Inc. For any queries regarding this Policy, please contact us:

**E-mail:** [privacy@moviesfanatic.com](mailto:privacy@moviesfanatic.com)

**Snail Mail:** Aztec Media Inc., Attention: Privacy Policy Administrator, Post Office Box 51968, Limassol, Cyprus.
